http://www.livablecities.org/terms-of-use

ConsultationChild-Friendly Communities
Social and Health Impact Assessment (SHIA)
Terms of Use
International Making Cities Livable provides information on our website (the "Site") subject to the following terms and conditions (the "Terms of Use"). The terms "we," "our," "us," and "IMCL" refer to International Making Cities Livable. The term "you" refers to each individual user of this site and, if applicable to your use, your employer or firm. By accessing or using the site, you are acknowledging that you have read, understand, and agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by these Terms of Use and our Privacy Policy. If you disagree with these Terms of Use and our Privacy Policy (as amended from time to time) or are dissatisfied with this Site, your only remedy is to discontinue using this Site.PrivacyPlease review the IMCL Privacy Policy, which also governs your visit to the Site, so that you may understand our privacy practices.Scope and Accuracy of InformationIMCL attempts to be as accurate as possible when describing our organization and services on the Site; however, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we do not warrant that the services or content available on the Site are accurate, complete, reliable, current or error-free.Intellectual PropertyUnless otherwise noted, IMCL owns all content available on this Site, including but not limited to the text, photographs, images, graphics, audio clips, and any compilation or arrangement thereof (the "Content"). All Content is protected by United States and international laws regarding copyrights, trademarks, trade secrets and other proprietary rights. The trademarks, logos, and service marks displayed on the Site (collectively, the "Trademarks") are owned by IMCL, in the United States or other countries, and are protected by United States and international trademark laws. All other Trademarks not owned by us that appear on the Site are the property of their respective owners, who may or may not be affiliated with, connected to, or sponsored by IMCL.Limited LicenseIMCL grants you a limited, revocable, and non-exclusive license to access and make personal use of the Site. Please note that you may not frame or utilize framing techniques to enclose the Site or any portion thereof without our prior written consent. The limited license set forth herein does not include the right to: (i) copy, modify or download, other than as expressly permitted, the Site or its Content (except caching or as necessary to view the Content); (ii) make any use of the Site or its Content other than for your personal informational purposes, and if applicable, for informational purposes for your employer or firm; (iii) create any derivative work based upon either the Site or its Content; or (iv) use any meta tags or any other "hidden text" utilizing the name or Trademarks of IMCL without our express written consent. A website that links to our Site (i) may link to, but not replicate, our Content; (ii) may not imply that we are endorsing such website or its services or products; (iii) may not misrepresent its relationship with us; and (iv) may not link to any page of the Site other than the home page. IMCL may, in our sole discretion, request that you remove any link to the Site, and upon receipt of such request, you shall immediately remove such link. Any unauthorized use by you of the Site terminates the limited license set forth in this section without prejudice to any other remedy provided by applicable law.Links to Other WebsitesLinks on this Site may lead to websites maintained by individuals or organizations other than IMCL. These links are for your convenience only and are not an endorsement by us, our affiliates or our partners of the referenced content, product, service or website. We are not responsible for such websites or their content, and we make no representation or warranty regarding the accuracy, timeliness, suitability or any other aspect of the content located on such websites, and we do not monitor nor endorse such websites or content.Representations and Warranties; Limitations of LiabilityINTERNATIONAL MAKING CITIES LIVABLE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE RESPECTIVE DIRECTORS, PRINCIPALS, CORPORATE OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS AND REPRESENTATIVES MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, ABOUT THE ACCURACY, TIMELINESS, SUITABILITY OR ANY OTHER ASPECT OF THIS SITE OR ANY CONTENT ON OR ACCESSED THROUGH THIS SITE FOR ANY PURPOSE, ALL OF WHICH IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. IMCL HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES AND OBLIGATIONS WITH REGARD TO THE SITE OR ANY CONTENT ON OR ACCESSED THROUGH THIS SITE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND OBLIGATIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT, UNLESS AND TO THE EXTENT SUCH REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES ARE NOT LEGALLY EXCLUDABLE. IN NO EVENT SHALL IMCL, ITS DIRECTORS, PRINCIPALS, CORPORATE OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS AND REPRESENTATIVES BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, CONSEQUENTIAL OR OTHER DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LIABILITY FOR INTERRUPTION OF BUSINESS, LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS), WITHOUT REGARD TO THE FORM OF ANY ACTION, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTIONS, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THIS SITE, ANY CONTENT ON OR ACCESSED THROUGH THIS SITE, OR ANY COPYING, DISPLAY OR OTHER USE THEREOF.IndemnificationYou agree to defend, indemnify and hold IMCL harmless for any loss, damages or costs, including reasonable attorneys' fees, resulting from any third party claim, action, or demand resulting from your use of the Site.DisputesWith respect to any dispute regarding the Site, your rights and obligations and all actions contemplated by these Terms of Use shall be governed by the laws of the state of Oregon, as if the Terms of Use were a contract wholly entered into and wholly performed within Oregon. Any dispute relating in any way to your visit to the Site shall be submitted to confidential arbitration before a single arbitrator in Portland, Oregon except that, to the extent you have in any manner violated or threatened to violate our intellectual property rights, we may seek injunctive or other appropriate relief in Oregon, and you consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in such courts. The arbitrator's award shall be binding and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, no arbitration under this Agreement shall be joined to an arbitration involving any other party subject to this Agreement, whether through class arbitration proceedings or otherwise.Copyright ComplaintsIMCL respects the intellectual property of others. If you believe that your work has been copied on the Site in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please send us a message to notify us of claimed infringement.GeneralThis Site and its Content are made available only to provide information about IMCL. IMCL maintains this Site in Portland, Oregon, USA, and makes no representation that this Site or any content on or accessed through the Site are appropriate or available for use in other jurisdictions. You are responsible for compliance with all applicable laws and regulations. You acknowledge and agree that these Terms of Use, together with our Privacy Policy, constitute the complete and exclusive agreement between us concerning your use of the Site, and supersede and govern all prior proposals, agreements, or other communications. IMCL reserves the right, in our sole discretion, to change these Terms of Use at any time by posting the changes on the Site. Any changes are effective immediately upon posting to the Site. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your agreement to all such terms and conditions. In the event that any provision of these Terms of Use shall be unenforceable or invalid under any applicable law or be so held by any applicable court decision, such unenforceability or invalidity shall not render these Terms of Use unenforceable or invalid as a whole. IMCL will amend or replace such provision with one that is valid and enforceable and which achieves, to the extent possible, our original objectives and intent as reflected in the original provision. If you have any questions regarding these Terms of Use, please send us a message. Copyright 2010 International Making Cities Livable
"I know of no other conference which provides the international expertise."
Sylvia Sutherland, former Mayor, Peterborough, Ontario
"A wonderful Conference. I truly believe this is the best Conference on cities."
Mayor Joseph P. Riley, Jr., City of Charleston
"The most important continuous conference dialogue on making the world's cities and towns more livable for all of their inhabitants."
Dr. Sven von Ungern-Sternberg, Governor, State of South Baden, Germany
"The conference holds a magnifying glass to the world's best cities, revealing why, and how they work."
Benjamin Thompson, FAIA AIA Gold Medalist
"Love for our cities unites all of us in this unique, impressive conference, with participants from different countries, with different professional backgrounds, but with one purpose: making our cities more livable."
Antonio Casellati Former Mayor, City of Venice, Italy
"Ive learned more from this conference than any other conference that I've ever gone to. I've been a city councillor now for twenty years, and I'm so glad I went to that first one twenty years ago."
Kim Richter, City Councillor, Langley, BC
"Well-structured, extremely well-organized and super-high quality of both the presenters and materials presented."
Dr. Mirela Newman, Coordinator, Urban Studies Graduate Program, S Conn St. University
Read more...
©<?php echo date("Y") ?> International Making Cities Livable LLC. All Rights Reserved.
